You're not allowed to smoke on
the street around here, buddy.
Nice to meet you, Toriashi Shoma-san.
I'm Miyama Kirishima.
Is He Smart
or Stupid?
This isn't actually the first time,
is it? We've met before.
I've come to take Yoshino home.
How'd you even find her?
You been followin' us?
You know, maybe I have. I could've been.
Did you not notice?
You tryin' to start some shit?
Of course not. I wouldn't dream of
picking a fight with Yoshino's family.
If we got married, you'd be my brother-in-law.
That's a real shitty future, right there.
Whose orders are you actin' on?
Orders?
Do you think Boss Miyama's
the one setting my agenda?
I admit that Yoshino could be used
to spark a war with the west,
or, alternatively, as a deterrent.
But, unfortunately for you, that's
not why she was brought to Tokyo.
I will admit that Boss Somei
probably doesn't expect
Yoshino and I to get
married, at all, though.
He's trying to manipulate
me for personal reasons.
And I accepted his offer knowing that.
Granted, I plan on using him
too, so it's no big deal.
No big deal? So what the hell're
you even gettin' outta all this?
As long as I'm doing what Boss Somei
asks, Yoshino will be with me.
I'm in love with her, see? So in
that sense, she's irreplaceable.
Are you outta your damn mind?
Hey, what are you doing here?!
I came to to take you home.
It's kinda late, after all.
How'd you even know where—
Let's see it.
Sharp as ever, Yoshino.
I knew it...
This nut made a clone of my phone
and used that to get the location
info from the original.
Didn't I tell you to just call me
if you wanna know where I am?
And I will, next time.
You say that every damn time!
What?
Maybe you oughta come back
to Osaka with me after all.
Huh? Where's this coming from?
I'll explain to the boss. This guy
clearly ain't right in the head.
Well, you're right about that...
You're not going to leave, right, Yoshino?
You're gettin' in on this, too?
I think I'm the best
person for you to marry.
You even realize what you're sayin' here?
What do you mean?
You're clearly just a damn stalker!
You know, she's told me that before, too.
And yet she never went home.
I think that about sums it up.
This isn't something an outsider like
you gets to have an opinion on.
You...
Outsider?
You better watch your mouth,
there. Shoma is family.
If there's an outsider
here, it's you, dumbass.
You know, you're right.
I went too far. I'm sorry.
I guess it's fine.
I appreciate the concern, Shoma,
but things are okay for now,
so you can head back to Osaka on your own.
You're leavin' first thing in the morning
right? Better get to bed already.
I'm gonna head back with Kirishima.
Understood.
Well, I've gotta get my stuff,
so wait here for a sec.
Sure.
Shoma!
I made it. Ugh, so tired...
I said you didn't have to see me off.
What's up?
Where is he?
Oh, Kirishima? At home, probably.
I didn't tell him I was leaving.
You're pretty obvious, huh? You hate him.
Never did like chatty,
smooth-talker types, did ya?
What's your take on him?
He's crazy.
Yeah, sure enough.
But it feels like he's got too much of an
advantage right now, so I can't go back yet.
Gotta figure out some way to beat him.
That's what I don't understand.
Yoshino-san, you're willin' to give
up your own life before your pride
or breaking the rules you set for yourself.
I'm pretty sure about that.
Thank you for riding with Shinkansen.
Nozomi 203 for Shin-Osaka station
will now be pulling into Platform 16.
I oughta go.
Shoma! If I don't have my pride or
honor, then I don't have anything.
Without them, I may as well be dead.
That sounds like you.
But I could never risk my
life for stuff like that.
Then what would you risk it for?
You've got a bug in your hair.
A bug?! Get it out, get it out!
Wait, that ain't a bug.
Is it a crumb?
I-I had bread for breakfast, I guess.
Well, you're free to die or do whatever
else you like, just don't go overboard.
I get it, okay?!
I'm gonna try and figure out what the
boss is up to when I get back to Osaka.
Oh, about that stuff you
mentioned at the restaurant?
You think there's somethin' going on?
There's gotta be. You an' me
just don't know about it yet.
Well...
Have a safe trip back.
I'll drop by again.
Make sure to attend your classes.
Yeah, I'll do what I can.
Good way of lookin' at it.
I'm gonna try and stay on my toes, too.
It's really crowded today.
I heard there's a field day at
a nearby grade school.
S-So close. I can feel his body heat...
And he smells really good for some reason.
What's wrong? You feeling okay?
I'm trying to stay aware of my surroundings.
Aware... of what, exactly?
Well, in broad terms,
anyone trying to kill you.
What the heck?
Just being careful.
On the odd chance you end up
dead, I'll be killed, too.
Y'know, I think this might be my first
time riding in such a packed train.
I never mentioned before,
because I didn't want anyone thinking
I was sheltered and spoiled, but...
Before I came to Tokyo,
I would always get a ride to wherever.
But I didn't want people to see
a car waiting for me at school,
so I'd always have the
pickup be further away.
Except for my first year of middle school.
I walked then because Shoma was with me.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Where do I recognize that cold feeling
from? He gave it off before...
Wait. It was when I first got to Tokyo...
He had better not say he's
bored again! Pain in the ass!
Come to think of it, I haven't exactly been
workin' to make him fall for me, have I?
How to keep him interested
Are you high-maintenance and
dependent upon your boyfriend?
Men tend to get bored of women
they consider burdens.
Try and be less clingy and
obnoxious, and interact with men
other than your S.O.
That's no help at all!
I ate it in under ten minutes, so it was free.
I ate it in under ten minutes,
so it was free.
What the hell is he doing?
Study!
He was looking at me.
I'm not gonna be able
to wear this next year.
And I have to say...
It feels like I'm moving.
Maybe if I pack up right now,
I can just head back to Osaka?
No, no! That's not it!
I'm just organizing my stuff!
Man, why can't he be easier to predict?
I've come all the way back around
to bein' pissed off about it!
Pissed off about what, exactly?
Wh-What are you doing out here?!
Here. A delivery from Osaka.
O-Oh, okay. Thanks.
Wonder what it is. It's kinda heavy...
Are you heading out, Yoshino?
Oh, no. Since it's summer already
I was just going through my wardrobe.
Really?
It looks kind of like you're packing up.
Not good! I can't turn around.
The same feeling from this morning.
Maybe even worse...
Are you doing this on purpose?
Do you want to kill me?
Kill you, Yoshino? No.
Then what's your problem with me?
I don't have any problems with you, Yoshino.
Then are you bored of me again?
The thought hadn't entered my mind.
Wait... is it Shoma, then?
Is he what you're mad about?
I'm not sure. I've never really hated
someone before, so I can't say.
Then what would you do if I told
you he and I were going out?
That's fine.
Really? You mean it?
Yeah. I've arranged for my girls to be
with other guys plenty of times before.
So the idea of you having a good time
with some guy from Osaka
behind my back sounds great.
Do you mind if I set a stipulation, though?
Like what?
You're free to be with whomever you
want, Yoshino, and I won't mind.
But whatever you do, I want
you to do it in front of me.
You know how people talk about
the carrot and the stick?
Well, I don't mind there being no carrot.
Getting hit with the stick feels
much sweeter, anyway.
That's true in most cases, but not with you.
I fell hard for you, and can't
seem to ever get a leg up.
Which is why I want to make sure to
balance the carrot and the stick.
So, if you're going to cheat on me,
all of the sex and the kissing—
make sure to do it where I can see.
You can even tie me up if you want to.
And once it's over, I'll kill the other guy.
That way it all balances out.
Wh-What the hell're you talking about?
Are you outta your mind?
You're saying that if Shoma
and I really were going out,
you'd end up killing him in the end?
Are you going out?
Hell no, we're not! I just
told you he was family!
You don't believe me?
I do. I don't think there's
anything going on.
You do seem close for family, though.
What you saw was totally normal!
Except it's not normal, is it?
You're not even blood-related.
If you start picking at stuff like
that, there'll be no end to it.
I'm not blood relatives with anyone
I grew up with except Grandpa.
You're makin' it sound like you're
jealous of Shoma, y'know.
You know, maybe I am.
I hadn't considered that.
You may be right. I feel like
I'm going crazy from jealousy.
W-Wait, wait, wait!
Are you being serious right now?
You really are crazy.
How about I become normal, then?
I'll become your idea of a normal guy.
I don't really have a good idea how it'd
work, and I've never tried it before,
but for your sake, I'm willing to.
I think I can do a decent job, as long
as you tell me what to shoot for.
The hell?
So you're willin' to turn your life
upside down just to please some chick?
I'm not sure. Maybe?
Is that what I'd be doing?
I hadn't said anythin', but in the name
of fairness, all cards on the table.
My plan is that, after a year, I'm gonna
ditch you and head back to Osaka.
But I've made up my mind. On the
off chance that I fall for you,
I'm gonna stay in Tokyo.
Knowin' you, I bet you'd be able
to act like my ideal guy, all right.
But that sure as shit ain't
gonna make me fall for you.
Then what do I need to do?
"What do I need to do?"
Not the kinda thing I'd expect
to hear from a playboy like you.
If the alternative is
half-assing some normie act,
then you oughta be the craziest
bastard in the world instead!
That'd be a damn sight better!
If I'm being honest, even
though I love you now,
I figured I would get
bored of you some day...
But I was wrong.
As long as you never change,
I'll never stop loving you, Yoshino.
You really are crazy.
Thank you. This marks our
first step towards marriage.
Ugh, talking with you literally
makes my head hurt.
I'm gonna change and have dinner.
Want me to make dinner while you change?
Go back to your own room!
Every damn year...
Hilarious! You get sick every summer!
No wonder my head was hurting.
Guess I'll take today off school.
Good morning. I think I caught a cold.
It's not too bad but I'm going
to take today off from school.
You don't have to check on me,
so please, head to class on your
own.
Good morning, Yoshino!
Brought you some sports drinks.
I just happened to be running in the park
over by the main street when I got your text,
so I got these at the
convenience store over there.
That's over a kilometer away!
You mean to tell me you
ran all the way back?
And it's only been three minutes...
Seriously, this happens every summer.
It's practically a tradition.
Thanks. I'm gonna go grab
another sports drink.
How's your appetite? Should
I get you some gelatin or yogurt?
You'll be late if you try and
do more shopping.
I'm not going to school.
I'm staying here to look after you.
Whoa, no!
It's just a light fever!
It'll get better if I rest some!
What about the hospital? I can take you.
Something wrong?
I don't wanna go to the hospital.
Why not? It can't hurt to get checked out.
I don't like hospitals, so I don't want to go.
Didn't you just have a kidney removed?
My hatred for you helped
me push through that.
Wow, I gotta admit, I'm honored.
Okay, enough! Take your
ass to school already!
But...
I'll let you know if anything happens!
In that case, I'll message you every hour.
Just make sure they get marked as read.
And if you need anything, just
let me know. I'll rush back.
You're a real handful, y'know that?
How are you feeling?
Just finished fourth period.
One more class to go.
I'll make sure to be home by 5.
Sorry if you're sleeping, I let
Inamori-san know that you're not
feeling well, so if you need anything,
just ask him.
No response.
Sorry if you're sleeping, I let
Inamori-san know that you're not
feeling well, so if you need anything,
just ask him.
No response.
How's your fever?
A little higher.
Seriously?
How much?
How's your fever?
A little higher.
Seriously?
How much?
The person you have called is not available.
After the tone—
Miyama, lunch is ending.
Sorry, I've got something to take care of.
I'm going to talk to my homeroom
teacher about going home early.
Segawa
This is Segawa. It's been a while.
Sorry to bother you, but there's
something I'd like to discuss...
Segawa
Would you be able to come by
our place tonight? Waiting for your reply.
And you have absolutely no idea
where they've gone, Segawa-san?
N-Not yet.
Hello? Is this Tachibana-san?
This is Kirishima.
You know how one of the Higashi family's
guys made a move on their boss's girl,
and they ran off together, right?
You find them?
The owner of the brothel, who
was hiding them, contacted me.
They're on the run again.
I'll send you the address, so could
you have someone come down here?
Huh? Wait—
Where are you right now?
Saitama.
Apparently, this place doesn't
have anyone working it.
If we have one of our people on it,
we'll be able to collect protection.
I'll send someone, so don't move.
As fast as possible, please.
Yoshino got sick somehow.
I'm in a hurry to head
home and look after her.
She hasn't been responding
when I call, either.
The hell do I care?
Call an ambulance or something.
The thing is, she apparently doesn't
like hospitals. So, I'd rather—
Whoa, hold on! I called you
because you're not yakuza!
Right. I'm not yakuza.
But the person on the way right now is.
You didn't seriously think you
could solve yakuza trouble
without turning to yakuza, did you?
Even an idiot could figure that out.
The protection money also gets
you stuff like hot towels
and a selection of houseplants,
so look forward to it.
Oh, one other thing.
Yes?!
Do you know any good hospitals in the
city that see patients overnight?
Yoshino. I'm sorry I'm late.
Let me take your temperature.
Sorry, I know you're not feeling well.
Hello? Inamori-san?
Yoshino doesn't seem to be doing any better.
I'm thinking about taking her to
the hospital now that I'm back.
Would you mind driving us?
And if possible, could you crank
the AC in the car?
We're gonna take a little trip, Yoshino.
My head is spinning...
Are you feeling nauseous, Yoshino?
Maybe lying down isn't helping. Try this.
Smells nice...
What fragrance is this again...?
Good morning.
Sorry to bother you so early.
Do you have time to talk?
Yeah, I do.
Her fever seems to have broken.
Good, good, that's great news.
Appreciate you watchin' out
for Yoshino all the time.
She givin' you a hard time?
You could say that.
She calls me a stalker all the time.
That girl, honestly...
I couldn't tell ya who she took after,
but she's got a hell of a mouth.
Oh, I'm not complaining.
Most people would be uncomfortable
enough to have run off,
but I get the feeling she's
going to stay the entire year.
That right?
She does take after me in the weirdest ways.
I know I'm askin' a lot here, but take
care of her for the year, alright?
Yes, of course. I'll stalk her
or whatever else it takes.
That was the deal, after all.